<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage</title>
    <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khchen-hp.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Optimal control towards sustainable wastewater treatment plants based on multi-agent reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/projects/chem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/projects/chem/</guid>
      <description>Highlights  Multi-agent reinforcement learning was firstly applied for parameters optimization. Reward function was designed from LCA for sustainable optimization. Optimization under various discharge standards and emphasis was compared. LCA-driven strategy showed superiority on elimination of environmental impacts. MADDPG holds great potential and advantages to guide the operation of WWTP.  Abstract Wastewater treatment plants (WWTPs) are designed to eliminate pollutants and alleviate environmental pollution resulting from human activities. However, the construction and operation of WWTPs consume resources, emit greenhouse gases (GHGs) and produce residual sludge, thus require further optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimisation of wastewater treatment strategies in eco-industrial parks: Technology, location and transport</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/projects/che/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/projects/che/</guid>
      <description>Highlights   Mathematical optimisation of wastewater treatment/recovery in an industrial park.
  Bridges two-level design challenge on pipeline and resource recovery technologies.
  Systems approach to transport, topological features and circular economic aspects.
  Centralised and decentralised technology to treat and recover wastewater.
  Abstract The expanding population and rapid urbanisation, in particular in the Global South, are leading to global challenges on resource supply stress and rising waste generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>生态工业园区污水处理策略的优化：技术，位置和运输</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/cej/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/cej/</guid>
      <description>项目亮点   在工业园区中对废水处理/回收进行数学优化。
  连接管道设计和资源回收技术设计。
  系统方法优化运输，拓扑特征和循环经济。
  使用集中和分散技术来处理和回收废水。
  摘要（机翻） 随着人口的增长和快速的城市化，资源供应压力和污染物产生量不断增加。资源循环系统的转变以及对含碳和营养物污染物的可持续回收提供了解决此类挑战的方法。生态工业园区可以捕获各个污染物产生者之间的共生体，从而导致更有效的污染物回收方案。通过全系统设计，可以实现经济上有吸引力的方法，从而减少环境影响，同时提高高价值资源的回收率。在本文中，我们开发了一个优化框架以实现这种设计，从而允许考虑广泛的处理选项，以捕获技术和经济细节。除了技术选择外，该框架还考虑了空间层面，使用合适的运输网络设计。使用网络对各种情况进行了调查，突出了问题的多面性。在设计阶段需要考虑资源恢复的影响显得尤为重要。
关键词   污水
  资源回收经济
  优化
  生态工业园区
  链接 Elsevier
Arxiv
引用本论文 @article{o2020optimisation, title={Optimisation of wastewater treatment strategies in eco-industrial parks: Technology, location and transport}, author={O’Dwyer, Edward and Chen, Kehua and Wang, Hongcheng and Wang, Aijie and Shah, Nilay and Guo, Miao}, journal={Chemical Engineering Journal}, volume={381}, pages={122643}, year={2020}, publisher={Elsevier} } </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my homepage. I am currently a PhD candidate in IIP (Intelligent Transportation) at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, and my supervisor is Prof. Hai Yang.
I finished my Master study at Sino-Danish College, University of Chinese Academy of Sciences (SDC-UCAS) in June 2021. As a joint programme, I was also awarded Master of Science in Water and Environment from University of Copenhagen in Dec. 2020. My supervisors are Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: kehua.chen AT connect.ust.hk  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Spatio-Temporal Data Mining in Transportation  Kehua Chen, Jindong Han, Siyuan Feng, Meixin Zhu, Hai Yang. &amp;ldquo;Region-Aware Hierarchical Graph Contrastive Learning for Ride-Hailing Driver Profiling.” Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies. (IF=10.10, JCR Q1).  Driver Behavior Modeling  Kehua Chen, Xianda Chen, Zihan Yu, Meixin Zhu, Hai Yang. &amp;ldquo;EquiDiff: A Conditional Equivariant Diffusion Model For Trajectory Prediction.” IEEE ITSC 2023. Xianda Chen, Meixin Zhu, Kehua Chen, Pengqin Wang, Hongliang Lu, Hui Zhong, Xu Han.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>关于我</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/about/</guid>
      <description>欢迎来到我的主页。目前我是中国科学院大学中丹学院的硕士研究生，由中国与丹麦双方进行培养，我于2020年12月被哥本哈根大学授予了水与环境科学硕士学位，导师为王爱杰教授（哈工大&amp;amp;中科院）和Luca Vezzaro副教授（丹麦科技大学）。
我于2018年毕业于重庆大学，我的专业是土木工程，水科学与工程方向。2017年至2018年，我在伦敦大学学院土木工程学院进行访问交流，指导老师为白云教授。同时，我与帝国理工学院化学工程学院的郭淼博士合作完成了中欧交流项目，该项目为生态工业园区污水处理策略的优化：技术，位置和运输。
目前我的硕士研究研究是基于多智能体强化学习的污水处理厂可持续性最优控制。
2021年8月，我将成为香港科技大学的博士研究生，研究方向为智慧交通，导师为杨海教授。
教育经历   香港科技大学
智慧交通博士， 2021 - 2025
  哥本哈根大学 &amp;amp; 中国科学院大学
联合培养环境科学硕士， 2018 - 2021
面向可持续发展基于多智能体强化学习优化污水处理过程
  帝国理工学院 &amp;amp; 伦敦大学学院
化学工程与土木工程学院访问学生， 2017 - 2018
环境建模和污水供应链优化
  重庆大学
土木工程学士， 2014 - 2018
市政工程 （管网设计和水处理技术）
  项目经历   基于多智能体强化学习的水系统优化
项目负责人， 2019.9 - 至今
使用MADDPG来降低水系统的负面环境影响，实现优化控制
  观远数据暑期实习：算法工程师
杭州 2020.07 - 2020.08
使用LightGBM和线性规划来预测沃尔玛的销量和补货量
  Kaggle能源预测比赛： ASHRAE - Great Energy Predictor III</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>学术成果</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/publications/</guid>
      <description> Kehua Chen, Hongcheng Wang , Jinglong Han, Wenzong Liu, Haoyi Cheng, Bin Liang, Aijie Wang .“The application of footprints for assessing the sustainability of wastewater treatment plants: a review.” Journal of Cleaner Production (2020): 124053. (IF=7.25, JCR Q1, 4/210) Edward O’Dwyer, Kehua Chen, Hongcheng Wang, Aijie Wang, Nilay Shah, Miao Guo∗. “Optimisation of wastewater treatment strategies in eco-industrial parks: Technology, location and transport.”Chemical Engineering Journal 381 (2020): 122643. (IF=10.65, JCR Q1, 2/340)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>联系我</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/cn/contact/</guid>
      <description>欢迎关注我的Github、知乎以及领英账号！ 如果有任何的问题，也欢迎发送邮件来咨询！  邮箱：ckjzsa@163.com  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
