<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage</title>
    <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khchen-hp.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Optimisation of wastewater treatment strategies in eco-industrial parks: Technology, location and transport</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/projects/cej/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/projects/cej/</guid>
      <description>Highlights   Mathematical optimisation of wastewater treatment/recovery in an industrial park.
  Bridges two-level design challenge on pipeline and resource recovery technologies.
  Systems approach to transport, topological features and circular economic aspects.
  Centralised and decentralised technology to treat and recover wastewater.
  Abstract The expanding population and rapid urbanisation, in particular in the Global South, are leading to global challenges on resource supply stress and rising waste generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my homepage. I am currently a Master student in Sino-Danish College, University of Chinese Academy of Sciences. As a joint programme, I was awarded Master of Science in Water and Environment from University of Copenhagen in Dec. 2020. My supervisors are Prof. Aijie Wang (from HIT &amp;amp; CAS) and Associate Prof. Luca Vezzaro (from DTU).
I graduated from Chongqing University in 2018, and my course was Civil Engineering, mainly about Water Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Wellcome to follow me on Github, Zhihu or Linkedin. If you have any questions, just feel free to send me an email!  Email: ckjzsa@163.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://khchen-hp.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khchen-hp.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description> Kehua Chen, Hongcheng Wang , Jinglong Han, Wenzong Liu, Haoyi Cheng, Bin Liang, Aijie Wang .“The application of footprints for assessing the sustainability of wastewater treatment plants: a review.” Journal of Cleaner Production (2020): 124053. (IF=7.25, JCR Q1, 4/210) Edward O’Dwyer, Kehua Chen, Hongcheng Wang, Aijie Wang, Nilay Shah, Miao Guo∗. “Optimisation of wastewater treatment strategies in eco-industrial parks: Technology, location and transport.”Chemical Engineering Journal 381 (2020): 122643. (IF=10.65, JCR Q1, 2/340)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
